[SNORTS]
(Leonard:)Sheldon, don't make that noise.
It's disrespectful.
I should hope so.
It was a snort of derision.
You agree with me, right?
(Sheldon:)Loop quantum gravity
is the future of physics.
(Leonard:)Sorry, Leslie, I guess I prefer
my space stringy, not loopy.
(Leslie:)Well, I'm glad I found out the truth
about you before this went any further.
Truth? What truth?
(Leonard:)We're talking about untested hypotheses...
Look, it's no big deal.
Oh, it isn't? Really?
(Leslie:)Tell me, Leonard,
how will we raise the children?
I guess we wait until they're old enough
and let them choose their own theory.
(Leslie:)We can't let them choose, Leonard,
they're children.
(Leonard:)Wait, where are you going?
(Leslie:)I'm sorry.
I could've accepted our kids
being genetically unable to eat ice cream...
(Leslie:)...or ever get a good view of a parade.
(Leslie:)But this? This is a deal breaker.